[
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Franchise's Company",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Copyright's Company",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "event",
    "question": "Anda tertangkap basah merubah secara sengaja data keuangan, dikenakan sanksi mundur 19 langkah.",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -37,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Current Maturities of Lease",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Maturities of Obligations",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 3,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -2,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Witholding Taxes Payable",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Premium Liability",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Contigency Liability",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "event",
    "question": "Anda tidak berhasil memenuhi deadline, sehingga dikenakan sanksi untuk mundur 37 langkah",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 37,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase in Inventory Obsolence Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  }
]
